(upbeat music)
♪ See the stone set in your eyes ♪
♪ See the thorn twist in your side ♪
♪ I'll wait for you ♪
♪ Sleight of hand and twist of fate ♪
♪ On a bed of nails, she makes me wait ♪
♪ And I wait without you ♪
♪ With or without you ♪
♪ Through the storm, we reach the shore ♪
♪ You give it all but I want more ♪
♪ And I'm waiting for you ♪
♪ With or without you ♪
♪ With or without you, ah, ah ♪
♪ I can't live ♪
♪ With or without you ♪
(upbeat music)
♪ And you give yourself away ♪
♪ And you give ♪
♪ My hands are tied ♪
♪ My body bruised, she got me with ♪
♪ Nothing to win and
nothing left to lose ♪
♪ And you give yourself away ♪
♪ And you give ♪
♪ With or without you ♪
♪ With or without you, oh ♪
♪ I can't live ♪
♪ With or without you ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ With or without you, oh ♪
♪ I can't live ♪
♪ With or without you ♪
(upbeat music)
♪ Ooh ♪